preview of the next episode
You might say you might not need to use the Natsume sound or so much of it.
That's still an editing error.
I still need to be aware of where my place is when Takanashi is the main focus.
Shall we watch the rest of the episode?
I'm afraid to watch the rest of it.
Hello, this is Tokyo Tenson.
And Mr. Sakuma, I look forward to working with you today.
Pleased to meet you.
You've got a really cool face.
I'm at the peak of my fatigue.
I'm working on two Netflix shows, an Amazon Onebleu show, and a two-hour solo show for Fuji TV at the same time.
Take a break!
I'm going to be on "Matsumoto Nakai"!
I'm going to be a guest.
He's a guest.
Who are you going to talk with?
Hideaki Ito.
You really should take a break.
Mr. Sakuma is wearing plain clothes today.
I see.
Yes, sir.
It's nice.
It's fresh.
Fresh.
I'm going to the after-party of a wedding.
It's not an after-party.
It's six a week.
Six days a week.
I'm fine.
I'm just... you know... a teenage girl in her underwear...
What?
I'm afraid to say anything about the clothes of a girl this age.
I'm afraid to say anything about the clothes of a girl my age.
I can't say.
I don't know if it's okay.
Fujisaki's wearing something amazing.
And you're a fluffy girl, too.
Oh, that's her all-night stuff.
You're matching, Mr. Sakuma.
I have one too.
I heard you have it.
It's from Fufu-chan's "All Night Japan Zero" show.
Do you listen to the radio?
I listened to the radio once and got too excited.
I quit.
Then don't buy the merchandise.
I mean, I quit.
So, I'm going to be wearing my own clothes for this show.
This is the first time we're doing this.
We're going to watch a VCR that we shot on location.
I see.
Mr. Sakuma needs to be able to shoot on location.
This YouTube page has been viewed by many people in the industry.
I want this YouTube to be seen by people in the industry so that they'll want to hire Ruff Ruff for their work.
I want people to want to work with Ruff Ruff in the industry, so it's not just studio talk.
I want people to see me on location, not just talking in the studio.
That's right.
And the VTR of the location shoots they've done...
Mr. Sakuma hasn't seen the VTR of the location shooting that the members have done yet, right?
No, he hasn't.
So this is the first time you're seeing it.
Well, if there's anything that really bothers you...
I'd appreciate it if you could stop for a moment.
I'm not trying to be funny.
So you're saying it's okay to be angry in a normal way?
Yes, that's right.
Don't wait a minute.
Okay, okay.
Preview.
Do it like they did on TV Tokyo.
That's right.
Okay, that's fine.
How long is the VTR?
Nineteen minutes.
That's a big one.
It's a Golden Suburbs.
Okay, so this time...
Takanashi, Natsume and Nagamatsu.
Takanashi is sick today, so he's not here.
So we went to a very hot location.
I see.
Natsume, how was it?
It was a lot of fun.
Suddenly you're speaking one language?
That's the kind of thing people say when they're unsure.
How was Nagamatsu?
Yes, I did my best.
The hot ones, of course.
But the other parts were difficult too.
Oh, wow.
So there are some tricks?
Natsume's V-fly with Takanashi's impersonation?
Oh, V-furi.
That's right.
Then, Natsume, please do the V-furi.
Yes, this is Takanashi's long-cherished wish for a hot and spicy gourmet project!
I went there with Haru Nagamatsu and Ryuka Natsume.I went with Haru Nagamatsu and Ryuka Natsume!
Please take a look.
Oh, I said "eyes"!
Oh my god, that guy.
He's making fun of me!
Here you go, Takanashi Video Hot and Spicy Expedition!
Yay!
Let's see if everyone remembers what happened six months ago.
Six months ago?
Six months ago, I did a YouTube project.
I did a presentation about myself.
I did it! I did it!
The project I want to do is...
Yui Takanashi's hot and spicy food expedition.
Oh, wow!
That's why it's called a corps.
I want to take along members who are not good at spicy food.
I wonder who would be interesting to take along.
Maybe Natsume.
You don't like spicy food?
I hate it.
Is there someone like that with you?
How's today? Today.
I'm looking forward to it.
Take it easy.
Yui, you had a very tight schedule.
I had a schedule.
But I don't know... how hot it is.
I've never had anything like it.
I'm up for the challenge.
How hot can you get?
The hottest in Edofu
Jun-hot and
Momotaimen Nakamoto's
Hokkyoku Ramen and
I really want to eat ramen tonight!
If I go to a spicy restaurant this evening
I thought I'd hold off on the spicy food for lunch.
What? No way.
At 7-11.
"Momotaimen Nakamoto
Momota Men Nakamoto's ramen cup noodles.
I sold them... at lunch.
I chewed on them at school.
Amazing!
I'm so excited!
I just got a call from the staff.
You heard about it at the Takahashi promotion, right?
I'm not going to tell you the name of the restaurant until we get there.
But I knew of this place.
It's famous for its spicy food.
I'm so excited!
It's twice the price of the restaurant.
What?
I took too much.
I talked too much.
And so...
We've arrived at the restaurant.
The restaurant we're going to today is
Tingachisai!
Wow!
Amazing!
Authentic spiciness!
He's so happy.
I'm scared.
I've known about this place for a long time.
I knew of this restaurant.
It's a chain with several stores in Tokyo.
There's one in Yurakucho and one in Akihabara.
And in Akasaka...
There are two stores in Akasaka, but this is the first one.
It's called Gekkarindo.
Can we stop for a minute?
Let's stop for a minute.
I'm going to a very spicy place.
Takanashi is looking forward to it.
But Natsume and Nagamatsu...
Natsume and Nagamatsu both look like they're having fun.
the pretense is getting weaker.
That's why
when Takanashi is the main focus.
I have to be aware of where my place is
You have to be aware of where you are.
Other than the person who is the main person
If you don't know where your place is
It's hard to do the location and after this
And also, the road district is not going to be used anymore.
This is a really normal V.
If I was directing and watching.
I might not need to use so much of Natsume's sound and so on.
I might be like.
No one lies.
I just have to amplify my truth a little bit.
Being on TV means
Amplify the truth.
I just got my gold and silver.
Okay, let's all say it once.Okay, let's all say it once.
let's all say it one more time
Let's make it true.
That's right.
I'm learning a lot from this.
Let's watch the rest.
There's a show on TV called "Gekkarindo".
They even introduced it there.
This kind of information...
The fact that it's in there...
According to significant research.
They are famous for their hot bean curd.
Sounds spicy.
Spicy?
It's different from Bean Curd.
I imagine it's made with diced tofu.
It's probably very spicy and tasty.
It's kind of famous.
Can you stop for a second?
You've picked up the pace a bit.
What's wrong?
Natsume, I didn't understand a word you just said.
Well... you were right.
It was a jumbled mess.
You almost didn't explain normal Bean Curd.
Normally, it's a roll of bean curd.
It's like an emotion.
I'd have to go as far as that.
This is probably the spiciest and tastiest bean curd I've ever had.
They're famous for it.
Well, I'd like to go inside.
I'd like to go inside.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
Here we go.
What are you doing?
I'm in the mood for yakitori.
Look! Yakitori?
Oh, I'm blurting it out.
This is a good challenge.
Doing something?
It's important to do something.
Mr. Ikko...
Isn't this Arino Sashiharu?
I hope one day I'll be famous enough to get on your bandwagon.
Ruff Ruff.
Raise it higher and higher!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Hello. - Hello.
Hello, please.
Oh, you look happy
It's spicy but delicious
They say you can choose how spicy you want it.
What's this? It's a little one.
Jigoku-hot!
Hot as hell.
Is it hot?
Yes, it is!
The most popular among regular customers are...
KYAKUSHITA and SENGOKUHATSU.
Very hot!
But you came here today...
I came here with the intention of eating
I knew this place would be...
Scary, scary, scary
Scary, scary
Chewing on the wall
Scary, scary, scary.
Where did he go?
Look at them and tell me.
We'll all say it.
Well, that's okay, isn't it?
Looks painful.
Here you go, sir. Thank you very much for your patience.
Thank you very much.
Delicious.
Japan's first.
Close to 50,000 people
Everyone is here, but...
This one is more complete.
Thank you.
Hey, you.
You know what they say.
You say the bottom one's spicier.
Yes, it is.
You put it in there.
El Hale, you want some sauce?
Don't worry about it.
It's spicier on the bottom.
I was trying to get her to eat spicy food.
Okay, Takanashi Expedition.
First meal.
Ready?
Bon appétit!
Looks good.
Can I ask you to stop once?Can I ask you to stop once?
Yes, ma'am.
I think we should start with the weak ones.
Yes, that's what I thought.
If we don't start with the weak ones...
If we don't start with the weakest, we'll get eaten.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'll get eaten.
That makes Takanashi look really good.
Whenever I go on location.
When you go to idol groups...
It depends on who's playing the main role, right?
If Takanashi is the star this time.
If Takanashi is the star of the show.
It's important to eat first.
Understand?
Yes, I do.
Shall we continue?
Let's see the rest of it.
It smells so good.
Bon appétit.
That's a big bite.
Oh, my God.
Delicious.
It's hot as hell.
It's not spicy.
It's just that the chili peppers and raayu are really kicking it up a notch.
It's so good, it'll cheer you up.
That's amazing!
It's invigorating.
I feel like I'm energized.
It's so good!
Oh, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
How much did you eat? One bite.
Is it good?
Is it bad?
It's fine. It's fine.
Wait, that's too much.
Oh, thank God. I think I've got enough juice.
Oh, yeah.
Bon appétit!
It smells so good!
I'm scared.
What do I do?
Do you want this?
What? Hell?
From hell.
Oh, my God.
He's taking us back in time two.
It's on fire.
I've got a fight on my hands.
If you drink the drink, it'll make it worse.
Don't drink it. Eat it.
But I want a drink.
Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
But you know what, since you're here, and since you've given us the time of your life...
We have to make sure it's good, Pilar.
Yes, sir.
Good luck, Ryoka!
Taste good.
Don't be afraid, it's delicious!
Bon appétit.
Just a little bit.
Delicious
Great
Good job
Itadakimasu
It's hard.
It's quiet.
It's hard hard.
Let's stop once.
Natsume's reaction was easy to understand.
Nagamatsu, as I said before, if you really feel pain inside, you should show more emotion, right?
That's for sure.
Now, there is one more thing to edit.
Yes, wait a minute.
Not for the riffraff picture, but for the editing.
The second time Natsume is smiling, put it in later, and after she is in a difficult situation, she should try harder and appeal a little more.
You were laughing just a moment ago.
That was an editing error.
Editing error.
This is editing.
Let's see the rest.
Wait a minute.
This is going to go in all kinds of places.
This is the hardest thing I've ever experienced.
I've never experienced so much pain in my life.
You know what I mean?
Like Yugen.
I love it!
That's great. How do you eat so much?
It's hot.
I sweat a lot.
I like this, this is nice, the contrast, it's so crisp and clear
I knew it. Takanashi is responsible.I knew you had a sense of responsibility, Takanashi.
That's great.
He looks like he's eating well.
He'll finish it.
Oh, no.
You didn't eat earlier, right?
Yes, I did.
Can I drink this, too?
What?
Okay, I'll have some.
Why?
No, no, no, no.
You don't have to drink it.
Sweat.
Oh, I'm shaking, I'm shaking, I'm shaking, I'm shaking.
I'm scared.
Oh, my God.
Can you stop for a second?
Sure.
When Takanashi is drinking, we need to lick him and get a shot of their surprised expressions.
I have to press the camera.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. That's what I thought.
So, we should do a two-shot of them three days ago.
I'd better take them out, so I'll learn a little bit more about that part.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
But it's also in our power to bring in the camera.
Oh, right.
So when Takanashi takes that drink, if he surprises himself, he'll get the camera.
That's right.
You guys didn't bring in the cameras, either.
Yes, yes, yes.
The power to draw them in.
That's important.
Power.
This is going to be a learning experience for all of us.
hahaha
I feel like I'm being judged when I'm watching this V of ours.
Now I feel like I should talk a lot.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Chill finished his meal too!
Delicious!
Amazing!
Thanks for the food!
Keep up the good work!
Oh, man!
I'm going!
My body temperature is...
I'm bleeding!
I'm gonna get out of here!
You're making great progress, Haru!
That's great!
She's trying to eat it all!
That's amazing!
Wow!
Oh, man!
Wow! That's awesome!
Oh, man! That's amazing!
It's spicy, but you can tell it tastes good!
It's like that taste is so bad! The aftertaste!
Here we go!
Are you okay? I'm okay!
I thought I was gonna spill. Watch out.
I feel like a parent.
Even the kid's face.
Please applaud. It was delicious. Thank you.
There are two more.
These are the famous koyumemega ones, aren't they?
Looks delicious.
Wow.
The sauce is so red you can't see it.
I didn't know if it was at the beginning of the tofu.
Looks delicious.
In case you're wondering, it's used for tofu.
Tofu came out.
A little harder than yesterday's tofu.
Softer than rice curd.
With specially ordered tofu.
I still want a wow when it arrives.
Yes, that's right.
The reaction should be loud.
The second item of Gao Pear Super Spicy Charcoal Stuffed Tofu.
The restaurant's signature dish, Bean-curd soup with red bean paste.
Seino.
Bon appétit.
Looks hot.
Hot.
It's hot.
It's too hot.
Hot and spicy is too much.
It's good.
Are you okay? It's not too hot? You okay?
Not hotter than before?
I'm sure it's good.
I ate a lot.
But it's spicier than before.
It's spicy like it envelops you.
I don't know if it's enveloping.
It's getting a little blended in.It's getting a little confusing.
It's like a dragon or something has breathed fire into me.
Wow.
It's so good.
After it cooled down a bit.
It was too hot to eat.
Hot and spicy is pretty bad.
I can tell they're trying their best.
I'll do my best.
It's delicious. Delicious.
Ah!
I said with a grin.
It's delicious.
It's definitely better than before.
It was spicy and guttural before, but this is more like a spicy air,
but this one is more like an airy spiciness.
It's really spicy.
It's even hotter when you drink it.
Oh, it's hot.
That's right.
There's a little balance.
I'll go.
No, you're shaking.
You're laughing.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
It's buggy.
You're just having fun, aren't you?
People like that...
Cute smile.
It's spicy with a hint of mellowness.
I knew it would be delicious, but it's not the same at all.
It's so delicious!
Amazing.
It's not human.
They're listening.
I just finished my second bowl.
Can you eat?
Yes, I can.
It's good. It's good.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Good. Good.
delicious
Yum! Yum! Yum!
You look like a newborn.
That's what happens when it's too spicy.
That's right.
Are you okay? I ate it.
Thank you. Thank you.
Are you sure you're okay?
Ryoka-chan isn't very good with spicy food.
But today, he went out with me at my request.
I think I manned up and ate the rest.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Captain.
Nagamatsu. He's eating at the other tables.
I know you're doing your best.
But they forget they're idols.
He's eating at Pettak's.
Interesting. Not bad, not bad at all.
I finished Ryoka-chan's meal.
Thank you.
It was delicious.
Good luck, Kane-chan!
Good luck.
This is nice. Interesting.
He's quietly eating without listening to us.
Nagamatsu has the most normal face.
I'm so frustrated.
That's great.
It came so fast. The last one.
There's more.
I've got some feedback.
Looks delicious.
I'm kind of hungry.
I'm over the limit.
I shared some ramen with you.
Here it comes!
I wonder how many times
I'm going back for more.
I love spicy food
I'm a big eater.
I want to eat a lot.
Okay, Takanashi, let's go on a spicy expedition!
The first restaurant, the last three
Seino
Bon appétit!
So delicious!
Super strawberry
Mochimoka
Strawberry?
That's new.
Looks delicious.This looks good.
This looks delicious.
The texture of the noodles is new.
It's kind of delicious, but it's spicy.
Spicy?
It's a little more sour than before.
The texture of these noodles is totally different from the udon noodles.
The more you chew, the more flavor comes out.
These noodles are difficult to make, aren't they?
Difficult.
Weirdly delicious!
Very spicy!
That's good
If you chew it a little bit...
It's not spicy.
Oh, my God.
I'm going crazy.
I'm over the edge.
Yummy.
It's amazing.
Not too spicy.
I'm scared.
Want some? You don't want me to?
I'm going to try it.
Which way do you want to go?
Don't do it.
Ramayu.
You're going?
It's a test.
Challenge.
Challenge!
Good job with the challenge.
I'm afraid of raayu.
Ten billion points. Ten billion points already.
Let the younger generation do it.
We have a jump, règne.
We've got to crawl our way back up.
♪ Shine on, homeless Mario ♪
♪♪
It would be perfect if we could get
تمم I couldn't
cover
pou dou dou
circumstances
wh
wii
lar
blue
go for it!
Great eat up!
Something is rubbed into it.
It's like a hojiken
It's so good!
Then I'll be happy with the last bite!
Bon appétit!
Yes, it's ready!
I'm still looking at the menu.
You know, yesterday I was doing a lot of research on this restaurant.
Let's wrap it up.
Yes, everything from hell.
It's warm now.
It's so warm, it's like spring weather.
I'm so happy.
It was harder than I thought it would be.
It was so painful that I broke through the limit.
It's spring weather, or rather, it's spring.
Because we go to eat in spring
Spring weather
Be careful with this one, Takanashi Itcho
Because it's spring
Sakuma-san, I still want to go out to eat various hot and spicy food
I would like to go out to eat with our members
please make this project Negirakar!
Please do!
Is your luggage there?
Thank you very much.
I'll put it here.
Is that okay? Thank you very much.
I'll advertise it for you.
To the members who eat quickly.
Good.
It's always popular when people come to our store.
If I buy from you, does that mean you'll sell?
I'm sure it will.
Thank you very much.
Good luck. We'll be rooting for you.
Well, Mr. Sakuma, how was the total?
No, no, no. In total. Amazing.
It's amazing that Takanashi could eat that much.
And the two of them did a great job.
What's important is how to make people sympathize with the phenomenon before it happens.
How do we create our own pretense?
This is a challenge for both directors and entertainment
Let's do our best!
So, what did you think of the site?
I knew that you are good at spicy food.
but I didn't know you could make it that spicy.It's so spicy.
That I can eat it with a normal face and smile
I'm getting scared.
It was a bit too much, wasn't it?
How was Fujisaki?
My mouth went dry.
If you'd seen it...
Natsume's amazing, really.
You've awakened.
I've awakened. Yui's the captain.
I wanted to be the vice captain.
I worked hard to achieve it.
What happened to Nagamatsu?
He looked like a food fighter.
I was at my limit, too.
Yui Yui is a great eater.
He said he didn't like Lingqiao.
So everyone was like...
They were like, "Go for it!
I thought that if I said I couldn't eat it
I'd ruin it.
I see.
Everyone worked really hard.
I could feel it.
Thank you very much.
Now then, we've got some food for you, and it smells a little bit like flowers, doesn't it?
I didn't want to eat the three winners.
I didn't want to eat the 3Katsu... but I don't want to.
I ate a lot.
It's delicious.
Are you okay?
Well, in normal emotional terms, it's kind of painful, but...
But I think I've got the guts to put up with it.
It's not too spicy.
If you're asking me if I can do it or not, I can do it.
Wow, that's great.
How are you eating?
Wait a minute, what's that much?
Hey, Hibi...
What's that much?
You don't usually eat that?
I don't eat.
Hey, Hayashi's next to me.
It's like he's eating it as a side dish.
I'll only eat a little.
Bon appétit.
Aaaaah! Meboku!
Mmmm... but mmmm...
Awww...
What are you talking with!
You are disqualified as a reaction!
Awww...
Bon appétit!
You're shaking so much!
Oh my God.
I'm so scared.
How's it going?
Oh, no! Oh, no! It's bad! It's painful!
You're early!
It's good, isn't it?
It's pretty good.
I'll take it.
Ouch.
Oh, it hurts!
Oh, it's painful!
It's painful.
Spicy!
My mouth is too big
I can't close my mouth.
My mouth won't shut!
Not that much?
That's not good.
Oh, no.
I really didn't think people would eat it.
They're eating a lot.
Come on, come on, come on.
I'm out.
Oh, no. Mascot pattern?
Which one? Is it good?
Is it good?
Oh, here we go.
Oh, my God!
Wow! I didn't know you were the type.
It's not too spicy?
I don't know.
I think it might be getting a little spicy.
I didn't know.
Fresh!
You don't like it?
The smell is so bad.
A little. A little.
A little bit is fine.
Oh... ah...
I'm sorry.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Oh... my mouth... is popping!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Surprisingly, it didn't work.
But the meat is delicious.But the meat is delicious and flavorful!
You've got to do a food report!
Do you want to do the food report properly?
Come on, Mr. Sakuma!
I'd like you to make a final decision on whether or not to make this a regular feature.
Aya Takahashi's Ekkala Expedition!
Gum keyfee, everyone!
Reaction Koshi is disqualified!
My mouth is starting!
We are going to make it regular!
Takahashi will remain, and we will change the other two members in various ways!
That's what's going to happen, Fujisaki and...
That's right.
You're going to be a regular at that?
Thank you for watching until the end today.
Thank you!
It was!